M. HAMZA ALI FEROZI

Game Developer

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Game Developer with 2+ years of experience in all aspects of game development, single-player and multi-player functionalities. Passionate in game development and game designing. Expertise in component-based programming, SOLID principles, planning, debugging, and testing. Great capacity for learning and implementing new programming languages.

EXPERIENCE

GAME DEVELOPER (Unreal Engine)

EPaging (Pvt) LTD, Karachi / March 2022 - Present

- Implementing multiplayer functionalities using blueprints.
- Implementing APIs and server-side functionalities.
- Documenting MOMs and requirements gathering.

GAME DEVELOPER (Unity)

The Game Storm Studios (Pvt) LTD, Karachi / March 2020 – March 2022

- Supported games with 10k+ active users.
- Made D1 reach 25% by designing and implementing levels.
- Boost company revenue by integrating Ad-SDKs with an extended behavior algorithm.
- Full cycle of the software development process from concept to publishing.
- Provided highly optimized code.
- Team Management and cooperation.
- Manage records, analyzed level progression, and iterate according to it.
- Implemented racing games using a Realistic Car Controller.
- Designed and implemented AI behavior for the FPS shooting game.

INTERN

The Game Storm Studios (PVT). LTD, Karachi / January 2020 – March 2020

- Hands on experiences with projects on Unity 5 and above.
- Calling ads and testing ads and integrating 3rd Party APIs.

INDIE GAME DEVELOPER

Personal, Karachi / January 2019 - Present

- Designed and implemented a story-based game that runs on PC and controlled through Mobile device.
- Implemented a Faux gravity based Endless car game.
- Implemented an endless Shooting game.

- <u>designerali54@gmail.</u>
- +923342465557
- **♀** 75900-Karachi, Pakistan.
- in <u>linkedin.com/in/m-hamza-</u> ali-ferozi-
- iamferozi.github.io

SKILLS

Problem Solving

Photoshop

Blender

Strong Work Ethic

Time Management

Documentation

Critical Thinking

Researching

Audacity

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (COMPUTER SCIENCES)

2016 – 2020

Sindh Madrassah-

tul-Islam University,

Karachi.

HIGH SCHOOL (PRE-ENGINEERING) 2014 –

2016

P.E.C.H.S Govt

Science College.